hotnessrater.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy

As part of your registration, we collect your e-mail and ip address. This is used only to provide you with a user account, and for us to contact you if necessary. 

Your information will never be shared with or sold to any other parties except under the following circumstances: 

  * It is required by law to share the information with the appropriate agencies 
  * Hotness Rater is merged or acquired by another company. In this case, your information will be transferred to the new company and it will be subject to their privacy policy. 

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy. We will notify you of any significant changes in the way we treat personal information by e-mailing the e-mail address you provided on registration

## Advertising

HotnessRater.com displays advertisements provided by third-party advertising networks. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which may interest you. Links to each advertising network or their privacy policies are provided below:

For general information on consumer privacy on the web as it pertains to advertising, you may wish to visit the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). The NAI also provides information and resources on “opting-out” of behavioral advertising.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## Analytics

HotnessRater.com uses third-party analytics services to collect statistics about website visitors (for example, number of pageviews on a given day, or number of visits from a particular country during a given week). This information is used to determine the popularity of individual pages and sections. Links to each analytics service’s respective privacy policy is provided below:

If you have any questions or concerns feel free to contact us
